Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - Cataloged individually
        - You're so right for me, 1977; SR-7162-7163; Eastside Connection (Musical group) (Box 16)
          Rainbow marbled disc.
          Rampart Records
        - Praise you, 1999; SR-7176-7177; Fatboy Slim, 1963- (Box 16)
          Astralwerks/Skint
        - Pyromania, 1983; SR-7180-7181; Def Leppard (Musical group), (Box 16)
        - Genius rap; Genius of love, 1981; SR-7212-7213; Dr. Jeckyll & Mr. Hyde (Musical group) (Box 16)
        - Meet the beat., 1979; SR-7230-7231 (Box 16)
          Inner City Records of Washington
          Washington, DC
        - Throwdown; School beats, 1983; SR-7236-7237; Disco Four (Musical group) (Box 16)
        - Equality, 1981; SR-7240-7241; Five Points (Musical group) (Box 16)
          Applegold
        - Super rock body shock, 1980-1989; SR-7248; Eye Beta Rock (Musician) (Box 16)
          H.E.R.O. Records
          Westville, New Jersey
        - Clock on the wall., 1984; SR-7675 (Box 16)
        - Rocking & swing, 1979; SR-6947; General Echo, 1955-1980, (Box 17)
          Manhattan
        - In search of ..., 1977; SR-6977; In Search of Orchestra. (Box 17)
          A.V.I. Records
        - Cuba; Cuba: instrumental., 1978; SR-6985-6986; Gibson Brothers (Musical group) (Box 17)
        - Come on do it some more; Dance groove, 1977; SR-6989; Jones, Juggy Murray, 1923-2005. (Box 17)
          From the Jupiter LP#1401 "Rhythm And Blues".
          Ju-Par Records
        - Songs in the attic, 1981; SR-6990; Joel, Billy. (Box 17)
        - Roy Lee Johnson and the Villagers., 1973; SR-6998; Johnson, Roy Lee. (Box 17)
        - Warm leatherette., 1980; SR-6999; Jones, Grace, (Box 17)
        - Victim of love., 1979; SR-7003; John, Elton. (Box 17)
        - World within., 1979; SR-7018; Hooper, Stix. (Box 17)
        - So fine, 1982; SR-7021-7022; Kashif, (Box 17)
        - Knee deep; Doin' it, 1979; SR-7031; Hancock, Herbie, 1940- (Box 17)
        - Too hot to handle, 1976; SR-7040; Temperton, Rod. (Box 17)
        - Brotherhood, 1969; SR-7042; Harvey Averne Band. (Box 17)
        - Walk, 1979; SR-7049; Higgins, Chuck. (Box 17)
        - Greatest hits, 1968; SR-7057; Hendrix, Jimi. (Box 17)
        - 12" of pleasure., 1980; SR-7058 (Box 17)
          Greedy Recording Ltd.
        - Mr. Everything., 1982; SR-7070-7071 (Box 17)
          Sweet Mountain Records
        - It feels so good, 1980; SR-7087; Irie, Welton. (Box 17)
          JML
        - Different drummer, 1977; SR-7111; Song, Rahni. (Box 17)
          EMI-Manhattan Records
        - Space walk: Radio, 1980; SR-7118; Disc & That (Musical group) (Box 17)
          Willkerr
        - Straight out the jungle, 1988; SR-7174-7175; Jungle Brothers. (Box 17)
          Warlock
        - Abacab, 1981; SR-7178-7179; Genesis (Musical group), (Box 17)
        - Fire it up., 1979; SR-7186-7187; James, Rick, 1948-2004. (Box 17)
          Gordy
        - Ooh, la, la; No one home in the city, 1979; SR-7192-7193; Lane, Suzi. (Box 17)
        - Isaac Hayes-- to be continued., 1970; SR-7200-7201; Hayes, Isaac. (Box 17)
          Enterprise
        - Just a groove; We've got to make it, 1980; SR-7204-7205; Adams, Glen, 1945-2010. (Box 17)
          Sam Records
          Long Island City, New York
        - Lady of the night; Gotta get out of here, 1978; SR-7222-7223; Hawkins, Lucy (Musician) (Box 17)
        - Pop goes the captain, 1979; SR-7224-7225; Captain Sky. (Box 17)
        - Gerson King Combo. II, 1978; SR-7226-7227; Combo, Gerson King. (Box 17)
        - Girls., 1982; SR-7228-7229 (Box 17)
          Tabu
        - Winners., 1979; SR-7232-7233 (Box 17)
        - Lookin' through the windows, 1972; SR-7258-7259; Jackson 5 (Musical group) (Box 17)
        - Hit the road Jack., 1976; SR-7404 (Box 17)
          Trojan
        - Cold fire, 1982; SR-7473-7474; Gypsy Lane (Musical group) (Box 17)
          Musicor Records
        - Control yourself cousin, 1989; SR-7478-7479; Homeboy (Musician) (Box 17)
          White label. Title from sticker on disc label.
          C.T. Records
          England?
        - Laidback EP., 1996; SR-7602-7603; Laidback (Musician) (Box 17)
          Bolshi Records
        - Get crunked up, 2001; SR-7620; Iconz (Musical group) (Box 17)
          "Promotional copy; not for sale."
          Kudu
        - When push comes to shove, 1986; SR-6953; Maga (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Paramount Records
        - Kingdom of madness, 1978; SR-6954; Magnum (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Jengou Records; African Record Centre Distributors
          Brookly, New York
        - Living ornaments '79, 1981; SR-6967; Numan, Gary, 1958- (Box 18)
        - TSOP (The sound of Philadelphia); Love is the message, 1979; SR-6970; MFSB (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Promo, reissue of 1973 recording later released as a 12" single.
        - My revenge (Revenge is bad), 1981; SR-6976; Midtown Madness (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Sound Effects Records Inc.
        - Keep on dancing (Country style swing. Vol. 1), 1981; SR-6978; Nashville Rhythm Section. (Box 18)
          King Records
        - No, no, no; Dogtown; I don't know why; She gets down on her knees, 1981; SR-6979-6980; Ono, Yo¿¿ko. (Box 18)
        - Voices inside my head; When the world is running down, you make the best of what's still around, 1980; SR-6983; Police (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Promotional copy.From the A&M album "Zenyatta Mondatta" SP-4831.
        - Bear witness., 1996; SR-6991 (Box 18)
        - Led Zeppelin., 1969; SR-7005; Led Zeppelin (Musical group) (Box 18)
        - Do it with style, 1976; SR-7007; Lewis, Webster. (Box 18)
          Promotional copy. Special disco version of the Epic single 8-50256.
        - Sweet charity., 1970-1979; SR-7017; Coleman, Cy. (Box 18)
          Decadent Records
        - Clones of Dr. Funkenstein, 1976; SR-7043; Parliament (Musical group) (Box 18)
        - Matrix of compassion, 1982; SR-7045; Men (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Autistic Records
        - Osmium, 1970; SR-7060; Parliament (Musical group) (Box 18)
        - Magic trick; Good luck charm, 1977; SR-7077; Ohio Players (Musical group) (Box 18)
        - Jump on it., 1981; SR-7078; Ozone (Musical group) (Box 18)
        - Heartbeat of the Congo, 1961; SR-7079; Onago. (Box 18)
        - Give your body up to the music, 1979; SR-7080; Nichols, Billy. (Box 18)
        - Cruisin', 1979; SR-7081; Nesmith, Michael. (Box 18)
          Pablo
        - Funk be the flavour; Magic, 1996; SR-7082; Nookie. (Box 18)
          Urban Culture Recordings
        - Baby not tonight, 1981; SR-7083; Barnes, John, 1949- (Box 18)
        - Them changes, 1970; SR-7094; Miles, Buddy. (Box 18)
        - Soca earthquake, 1987; SR-7095; Montano, Machel. (Box 18)
        - Missy Missy Dee, 1980-1989; SR-7096; Missy Dee. (Box 18)
          Universal Record Company
        - Steel drums, 1970-1979; SR-7099; Native Steel Drum Band. (Box 18)
          Astor
        - You gotta get up, 1982; SR-7102; Majik (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Savoir Faire Records
        - After the party, 1985; SR-7106; Original Defosto himself, (Box 18)
          Charlie's Records
        - Papa's land, 1977; SR-7107; Sonny Okosuns Ozziddi (Musical group) (Box 18)
        - Drums, drums, drums, 1960-1969; SR-7109; OlatuNew Jerseyi, Babatunde. (Box 18)
          Roulette
        - Drums of passion, 1960; SR-7127; OlatuNew Jerseyi, Babatunde. (Box 18)
        - Black gold, 1978; SR-7128; Lord Nelson. (Box 18)
        - On my way, 1996; SR-7134; Palefield Mountain (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Buddja Records
          Mechelen, Belgium
        - Get cracking, 1980; SR-7150-7151; Kat Mandu (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Uniwave
          Montreal, Quebec
        - I'll tell you; Lonely woman, 1979; SR-7158-7159; Mendes, Sergio. (Box 18)
        - Special things., 1980; SR-7164-7165; Pleasure (Musical group) (Box 18)
        - Keep the dream alive., 1978; SR-7182-7183; Newman, David, 1933-2009. (Box 18)
          Jazz ensembles.
          Prestige: Distributed by Fantasy Records
        - Love magic., 1981; SR7188-7189 (Box 18)
        - Positive Force, 1980; SR-7194-7195; Positive Force (Musical group) (Box 18)
        - Best of the Meters, 1975; SR-7198; Meters (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Virgo
        - Meters., 1969; SR-7199; Meters (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Joe Gibbs Record Globe
        - Happy days; Tee's happy, 1981; SR-7206-7207; Northend (Musical group) (Box 18)
          Elektra/Asylum
        - Going west, 1982; SR-7234-7235; Members (Rock group) (Box 18)
        - I'm so hot for you; Still hott 4 u, 1982; SR-7460-7461; Orlando, Bobby. (Box 18)
        - Carnival time, 1984; SR-7652; Nite Blues Steel Band. (Box 18)
          Vista Sounds
        - I'll cast my fate to the wind, 1981; SR-6941; Snaps Montigo. (Box 19)
          Tune Wizard
        - What is it, 1994; SR-6946; S.O.U.L. (Musical group) (Box 19)
          Beat Goes Public
        - Lollipop man (Kojak theme '77), 1977; SR-6949; Robinson, Sylvia, 1936-2011. (Box 19)
          Test pressing, white label, recorded on one side only.Matrix etching: VI-314 NO-RE FWO.
          Vibration
        - Love you live, 1977; SR-6981-6982; Rolling Stones. (Box 19)
          Rolling Stones Records
        - Foster Sylvers., 1978; SR-7016 (Box 19)
        - Musicmagic, 1977; SR-7023-7024; Return to Forever (Musical group) (Box 19)
          Promotional copy.Taken from the Columbia Lp: Musicmagic PC 34682.
        - Da baddest b***h, 2000; SR-7027-7028; Trina. (Box 19)
          Slip-N-Slide Records: Manufactured and distributed by Atlantic Records
        - Sit up (long version); Monster fun, 1981; SR-7029-7030; Sadane, Marc. (Box 19)
          Promotional copy.A side is from the Warner Bros. album BSK 3503 One-way love affair.B side is from the Whitfield album WHK 3510 On the one.
          Warner Brothers Records/Whitfield Records
        - Prototype; Free me, 1996; SR-7038; Supafly (Musical group) (Box 19)
          Vibe'z Recordings
        - Go for it sucker, 1980; SR-7044; RG's All Nite Funk Band. (Box 19)
          Hotplate Records
        - Ripple., 1973; SR-7047 (Box 19)
          Gemini Records; Distributed by Charlie's Records
        - Give me your love, 1980; SR-7048; Striplin, Sylvia. (Box 19)
          Uno Melodic Records
        - Over and over; Party music, 1979; SR-7056; Torill. (Box 19)
        - We the people, 1972; SR-7084; Soul Searchers (Musical group: Washington, D.C.) (Box 19)
          Sussex Records
        - Can you feel it; Zone, 1976; SR-7088; Rhythm Makers (Musical group) (Box 19)
          Vigor Records
        - Get on up (get on down); Ocho rios, 1978; SR-7098; Roundtree (Musical group) (Box 19)
          OM Records
          San Francisco, California
        - Salsoul Orchestra., 1975; SR-7104 (Box 19)
        - Salsoul Orchestra., 1975; SR-7105 (Box 19)
          Ariola Eurodisc
          Barcelona
        - Give me your body while we're dancin'., 1979; SR-7112 (Box 19)
          Ken-Tone Records
        - Fast and nasty girl., 1991; SR-7117 (Box 19)
          Sunny Boy Records
        - 85555, 1982; SR-7120; Spliff (Musical group) (Box 19)
          CBS Schallplatten
        - Body music; Girl in Collinson, 1981; SR-7121; Rainbow, Chris. (Box 19)
          Lagos, Nigeria
        - Emotional rescue., 1980; SR-7133; Rolling Stones. (Box 19)
        - Hold tight, 1977; SR-7135; Robinson, Vicki Sue. (Box 19)
          From the "Odyssey" album, APL1-2204.
        - I just wanna do my thing; Mr. Davenport and Mr. James, 1977; SR-7146-7147; Starr, Edwin. (Box 19)
        - Charm; And yet again; Moscow motion, 1981; SR-7156-7157; Positive Noise (Musical group) (Box 19)
          Statik
        - Faces, 1977; SR-7170-7171; Szabo¿¿, Ga¿¿bor, 1936-1982. (Box 19)
        - Gang war, 1980; SR-7184-7185; Prince Charles and the City Beat Band. (Box 19)
          Solid Platinum Records
          Boston, Massachusetts
        - Hollyrock; Roll with it; Pump me up; E flat boogie, 1981; SR-7202-7203; Trouble Funk (Musical group) (Box 19)
          J&L Records
        - Disco-fied., 1976; SR-7210-7211; Rhythm Heritage (Musical group) (Box 19)
        - Sound of sunshine., 1975; SR-7218-7219; Casey, H. W. (Box 19)
          T.K. Records
        - Beat is fresh., 1985; SR-7238-7239 (Box 19)
          Sunnyview
        - Hot foot (a funque dizco opera), 1979; SR-7246-7247; Scales, Harvey. (Box 19)
        - Sensuous black man, 1970-1979; SR-7250; Moore, Rudy Ray, 1927-2008. (Box 19)
          Kent
        - Must be the music., 1981; SR7252 (Box 19)
        - Wham bam. 2: the 2nd massacre, 1992; SR-7443; Sagoo, Bally. (Box 19)
          Star Records
          Birmingham, England
        - Music sound better w, 2000; SR-7526; Stardust (Musical group) (Box 19)
        - Back on the right track, 1979; SR-7548-7549; Stone, Sly, (Box 19)
        - Hot tuna., 1996; SR-7602-7603; Pelirocco (Musician) (Box 19)
        - Calypso maestro, 1974; SR-7665; Sparrow (Calypso singer) (Box 19)
          Ra
          Mount Albert, Ontario
        - Lights out, 1984; SR-6943; Wolf, Peter, 1946- (Box 20)
          Promotional copy. Stamped gold lettering: Property of Capitol Records; B 484987.
        - Lights out, 1984; SR-6944; Wolf, Peter, 1946- (Box 20)
        - Ill centrik funk. Vol. 1. Chapter 3., 1998; SR-6961 (Box 20)
        - Total extrem; Do you?, 2004; SR-6968; WB's (Musical group) (Box 20)
          Road Rage Records
        - R&B acappellas., 1970; SR-6971 (Box 20)
        - Warm heart cold steel, 1975; SR-6972; 20th Century Steel Band, (Box 20)
          United Artists Records
        - Rising stars '87: from Sparrow's Young Brigade Calypso Tent., 1987; SR-7006 (Box 20)
        - Getting to the point, 1984; SR-7013; Vicious Four (Musical group) (Box 20)
          Billy-D Records
        - Koochy; Phreeknik, 2000; SR-7039; Van Helden, Armand. (Box 20)
          Armed Records
        - Point of no return, 1984; SR-7041; X-Posed (Musical group) (Box 20)
          Pacific Arts Corp.
          Carmel, California
        - DrumDrops. Volume four. The light rock album, 1979; SR-7051; Vieira, Joey D. (Box 20)
          Music Tree Corporation
          Whipple, Georgia
        - Stoned soul picnic, 1968; SR-7055; 5th Dimension (Musical group) (Box 20)
          Soul City
        - Ya mama, 1982; SR-7068-7069; WUF Ticket (Musical group). (Box 20)
        - Boogie beat, 1970-1979; SR-7085; Uno (Musical group) (Box 20)
          Tryon Park
          New Jersey
        - Drum drops: volume two, 1979; SR-7086 (Box 20)
          Music of Life
        - Kiss away; Laughter in the rain, 1977; SR-7097; Vitamin E (Musical group) (Box 20)
        - Shock treatment, 1974; SR-7110; Winter, Edgar, 1946- (Box 20)
        - Africa., 1960-1969; SR-7114 (Box 20)
          Mini Records
        - Rock it to me twice, 1982; SR-7115; Van Cleef, Lee (Musician) (Box 20)
          Island Visual Arts
        - Beat box, 1986; SR-7123; Vogel, Joy. (Box 20)
          TLO Records
        - Youngblood (Livin' in the streets); Keep on doin', 1978; SR-7124; War (Musical group) (Box 20)
          United Artists Music and Records Group
        - One more time., 1976; SR-7126; Watson, Ed (Musician) (Box 20)
          Port of Spain, Trinidad
          Brookyn, New York
        - Sounds of New York, U.S.A. Volume I: the big break rapper party., 1970-1979; SR-7130 (Box 20)
          Hip Hop Slam Records
          Oakland, California
        - Whispers greatest hits., 1975; SR-7138 (Box 20)
        - And the beat goes on; Can you do the boogie, 1979; SR-7139; Whispers (Musical group) (Box 20)
          Solar Records: Distributed by RCA Records
        - Bang a gong; Witch queen, 1979; SR-7140; Witch Queen (Musical group) (Box 20)
          Roadshow Records: Distributed by RCA Records
        - Goodnight tonight; Daytime nightime suffering, 1979; SR-7141; Wings (Musical group) (Box 20)
        - I like what you're doing to me, 1980; SR-7242-7243; Young & Co. (Musical group) (Box 20)
        - E.S.P., 1974; SR-7254-7255; Wylie, Richard Popcorn. (Box 20)
        - Technodelic, 1981; SR-7256-7257; Yellow Magic Orchestra. (Box 20)